Guide to the International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences Records 1970-1984
University of Chicago Library
- Series VIII: Publication Materials
  - Subseries 4: Conference Papers and Original Drafts
    - Simkin, Demitiri B., draft, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Shur, L.A., draft, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Sicard, H. von, draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Siverts, H., conference paper, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Slama-Cazacu, Tatiana, draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Smirnova, Ya.S., draft, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Shmelyova, M.N., draft, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - Shchekochikina, L.K., draft, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - Shaniyazov, K., draft, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Sohn, P., draft, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Solenberger, Robert R., draft, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Sorenson, E. Richard, and Allison Jablonko, draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Southworth, J., draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Spain, Jayne B., draft and abstract, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Spyridakis, Georgios, draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Stevens, Frank, draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Stopa, Roman, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Stratanovich, G.G., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Sukdeo, I., draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Szalay, Frederick S., draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - T, Tavares de Lima, Rossini, conference paper and translation, 1973 Taylor, J. Garth, conference paper, 1973 Taxami, Ch.M., conference paper, 1973 Thoreson, Timothy H.H., conference paper, 1973 Tiffany, Walter W., conference paper, 1973 Ting, Nai-tung, draft, 1973 Todorov, Tzvetan, Tokudome, M., conference paper, 1973 Torres de Aruúz, Reina, draft, 1973 Tubaki, Koszi, reprint, undated Trivedi, Harshad, conference paper, 1973 Trofimova, A.G., conference paper, 1973 Tsioli, Soy Marie, conference paper and translation, 1973 Turnbull, H.F., and R. E. Taylor, conference paper, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Tavares de Lima, Rossini, draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Tefft, Stanton K., draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Urdaneta, María-Luisa, draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - VA-VAR, Van Dam, André, conference paper, 1973 Van Dijk, Teun A., manuscript, 1972 Varagnac, A., conference paper, 1973 Vareene, Herve, conference paper, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - VAU-VE, Vaughan, Mary K. manuscript, 1973 Vendler, Zeno, draft, 1973 Verdier, R., draft, 1973 Verma, K.K., draft, 1973 Vessuri, Hebe M.C., draft, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - VI-VY, Viires, Ants, conference paper, 1973 Vilakazi, Absolom L., conference papers, 1973 Virsaladse, Elene B., conference paper, 1973 Vlachos, Evan, draft, 1973 Voight, Vilmos, conference paper, 1973 Von Mering, Otto, and Sally Ann Lawson, conference paper, 1973 Voronov, A.A., conference paper, 1973 Vyhnánek, L., conference paper, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Vaadenberg, Steven G., draft, undated (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Vandevort, B., draft, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Vergenes, H., C. Bouloux, draft, illustrations, and conference paper, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Verhaar, John W.M., draft, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Vermeersch, Etienne, draft, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Veronesi, Fosca Maruzzi, and Maria Zannoti, conference paper, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Vessuri, Hebe M.C., and Santiago A. Bilbao, draft, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Vidyarthi, L.P., draft, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Vine, Ion, draft, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Virsaladze, Helena B., 1972 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - WA-WEI, Wang, Sung-hsing, draft, 1974 Watanabe, Shoji, draft, undated Watson, Patty Jo, draft, undated Weiner, Janet Esser, conference paper, 1973 Weisner, Thomas S., draft, 1973 Weissleder, (Weinstien), (Vajnshtejan), S.I., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - WER-WES, Werner, Oswald, draft, 1973 Wescott, Roger W., drafts, undated West, Frederick Hadleigh, conference paper, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - WH-WR, Whiteford, Scott, draft, 1974 Widstrand, Carl Gösta, reprint, 1973 Wik, Reynold M., conference paper, 1973 Wilden, Anthony, draft, undated Williams, G., draft, 1973 Williams, Glyn, conference paper, 1973 Wingeyer, D., draft, undated Witkowski, Stanley, 1973 Wolf, Joseph, draft, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Wachuku, Alozie N. draft, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Weltfisch, Gene, manuscript, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Welinder, Stig, draft, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Wet, J.M.J. de, and J.R. Harlan, conference paper, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Woods, Clyde M., draft, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Wright, H.E., draft, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Young, C.C.S., draft, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Y, Yonemura, Shoji, conference paper, 1973 Younis, Abdelhameed, draft, 1973 Yurghinis, Yu.M., conference paper, 1973 Yurovskaya, Vz., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Z, Zamiti, Khalil, draft, undated Zaongo, B.J., conference paper, 1973 Zhornitskaya, M.Ya., conference paper, 1973 Zinich, V.T., conference paper, 1973 Zlatkovskaya, T.D., conference paper, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Znamierowska-Prufferowa, reprints and correspondence, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 5: Proceedings for World Anthropology Publications
    - Afterthoughts, queries about World Anthropology publication, 1980-1981 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Camara, Sory, drafts and illustrations, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Causdiet, Eugene, list of papers, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Cloak, Ted, preparation for proceeding, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Condomin, Georges, draft, undated (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence between editors, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence regarding proceedings, 1978 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Mayor Daley's proclamation for the ICAES, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Editor's recommendations, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Comments on Maurice Freedman's paper, 1973-1974 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Comments by Maurice Freedman, 1973-1974 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Comments by Maurice Freedman, 1973-1974 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Comments by Maurice Freedman, 1973-1974 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Hirschfield comments, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Hirschfield comments, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Information for authors, undated (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Inquiries for proceeding volumes, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Introduction to abstract volume, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Introductions, "C," drafts for editors, undated (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Introductions, "C," drafts for editors, undated (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - of papers, undated (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - of papers, undated (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - of papers, undated (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - "K," IUEAS business and plenary session, address by Vine DeLoria, 1973-1978 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - "M," feedback, summaries of conference, drafts, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Master list of papers in published volumes, 1972 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Master list watching papers and World Anthropology books, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Comments on William McNeill's paper, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Neuberger, Gay, proceedings volume, 1980 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Notes on proceedings, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Ordering of the program sections, 1973-1980 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Original materials for the proceedings volume, 1973-1982 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Original materials for the proceedings volume, 1973-1982 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Original materials for the proceedings volume, summaries by authors, 1973-1982 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Orphans, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Orphans, correspondence and draft, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Orphan list, undated (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Orphan lists, conference papers, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Outer office location index, undated (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Paper inventories, 1973-1975 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Conference papers nominated for proceedings, 1977, Albó, Xavier, 1973 Antler, Ellen and James Faris, 1973 Aronoff, Myron J., 1973 Bajema, Carl Jay, 1973` Borgonini-Tarlli, Silvan, and Giorio Paoli, 1973 Casteel, Richard W., 1973 Cloak Jr., F.T., 1973 Fry, Gary F., 1973 Ghabbour, Samir I., 1973 Goldberg, Harvey E., 1973 Gunawardena, K.L., 1973 Inokuchi, S., 1973 Jackson, Anthony, 1973 Johnson, Twig, 1973 Kurt, Donald V., 1973 Martin, Kent, O. 1973 Whitten Jr., Norman E., 1973 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Conference papers nominated for proceedings, 1977, Cookey, S.J.S., 1973 Fürer-Haimendorf, Christoph von, 1973 Haydu, Georges G., 1973 Magubane, B., 1973 Mahapatra Sitakant, 1973 Mead, Margaret, 1973 Molhotra, K.C., 1973 Morris, Laura Newell, and Peter E. Nute, 1973 Nah, June, 1973 Nusbaum, Geoffrey, 1973 Salzano, Francisco M., 1973 Schffler, H.W., 1973 Szalay, Lorand B., and Vid Pecjak, 1973 Terry, Emanuel, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Conference papers nominated for proceedings, 1977, Bartstra, C.J., 1973 Danielson, Ross, 1973 García, María-Pilar and Rae Lesser Blumber, 1973 Harrison, Tom, 1973 Jahan, Rounaq, 1973 Laver, John, 1973 Ramos, Carlos, 1973 Robineau, Claude, 1973 Salisbury, Richard F., 1973 Yngve, Victor H., 1973 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Conference papers nominated for proceedings, 1977, Berghe, Pierre L. van de, 1973 Brigard, Emilie de, 1973 Cohen, Mark N., 1973 Davie, Kenneth, 1973 Despres, Leo A., 1973 Everett, Michael W., 1973 Gifford, James C., 1973 Marriott, McKim and Ronald B. Inden, 1973 Muller, Jon, 1973 Skinner, Elliott P., 1973 Stoller, Marianne L., M. Jane Cauvel, 1973 Wing, Elizabeth S., 1973 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Conference papers nominated for proceedings, 1977, Bökönyi, S., 1973 Bornstein, Annika, 1973 Crabtree, Don E., 1973 Karp, Ivan, 1973 Prince Peter of Greece and Denmark, H.R.H., 1973 Freilich, Morris, 1973 Pollock, Nancy J., 1973 Purdy, Barbara A., 1973 Shimkin, Demitri, an dFloria J. Louie, 1973 Sozan, Michael, 1973 Thoresen, Timothy H.H., 1973 Weisner, Thomas S., 1973 Willner, Dorothy, 1973 Wilson, Christine S., 1973 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Conference papers nominated for proceedings, 1977, Miles, Douglas, 1973 Newell, William H., 1973 Shimkin, Louie and Frate, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Payroll, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Pre-congress conferences, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Pre-congress conferences, undated (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Preparation for proceedings, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Preparation for proceedings, correspondence with Ted Cloak, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Preparation for proceedings, correspondence with Ted Cloak, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Preparation for proceedings, correspondence with Ted Cloak, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Preparation for proceedings, comments on M. Freedman and comments by M. Freedman, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings Volume, organization and materials, 1975 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Proceedings Volume material, outlines, notes, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Proposed papers, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Publication status of WA volumes, undated (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Publications, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Publishing, correspondence, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Selections, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Tax, Sol and Gay Neuberger, outline, undated (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - World Anthropology, undated (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - World Anthropology, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - World Anthropology, see oversize for reprint chart, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - World Anthropology Books, 1973-1976 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - World Anthropology, catalogues, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - World Anthropology, comments, 195-1976 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - World Anthropology, drafts, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - World Anthropology, dual publications, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - World Anthropology, editors, 1976 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - World Anthropology, editors, 1976-1980 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - World Anthropology, editors, 1976-1980 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - World Anthropology, French translations, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - World Anthropology, Igwia Newsletter, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - World Anthropology, paper list, undated (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - World Anthropology, reorganization of files, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - World Anthropology, reviews, 1977 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - World Anthropology, reviews, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - World Anthropology, series, table of contents, 1974-1977 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - World Anthropology, series, table of contents, 1974-1977 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - World Anthropology Volume prefaces, first 24 volumes, 1974-1975 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - World Anthropology Volume prefaces, 1974-1976 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - World Anthropology, (North) West Africa, contributions in French, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - World Anthropology, (North) West Africa, contributions in French, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - World Anthropology, West Africa, manuscript, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - World Anthropology, J Whetsel, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Unpublished proceedings volume, section 1, the books, 1973 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Unpublished proceedings volume, section 2, plenary sessions, 1973 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Unpublished proceedings volume, section 3, feedback and organization, 1973 (Box 133, Folder 3)
- Series IX: Oversize
  - American Folk Concert, leaflet mock-up, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Tamu-Tamu, brochure mock-up and printed version, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Map, Detroit ethnic groups, by Sol Tax and Engrid Fogel, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Program, picture chart, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Special events, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Reprint chart, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Membership list for proceedings volume, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Atkinson, Jourdon, poster, "To All Black Citizens of Houston," 1973 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Lecourt, M., poster, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Z, Zamiti, Melika, draft, undated Zelmelman-Merino, Hugo, draft, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Petrshyn, J.T. reprint and correspondence, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Paper requests, undated (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Rolled timeline, "Hombrecer-Alienogenesis y Desalienacion, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 13)
- Series X: Audio
  - David, 5" reels 1 and 2 (Box 135)
  - Family seminar, 7" reel (Box 135)
  - Religion, 7" reel (Box 135)
  - Small group dis. Of religion/family, 7" reel (Box 135)
  - Conclusion of Family Rel., 7" reel (Box 135)
  - War and Peace, 7" reel (Box 135)
  - Family/Education, 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Urbanization, 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Urbanization, large group and small group, 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Opening of Youth for Mankind (YFM), 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Opening, 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Family in small groups/family-large groups, 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Good music, 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Small group discussion on religion, 7" reel (Box 136)
  - Cassette recordings of sessions. (Box 137)
  - Cassette recordings of sessions. (Box 138)
  - Cassette recordings of sessions. (Box 139)
- Series XI: Restricted
  - Student papers, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Financial information, 1970's (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Financial information, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Financial information, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Financial information, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Financial information, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Financial information, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Financial information, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Financial information, 1972 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Financial information, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - Financial information, 1975 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Post congress employee, 1975 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Letters from employees to Sol tax, regarding raises and resignations, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - IRS, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Financial information, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Financial information, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Financial information, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Alan Lomax, Financial information, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Financial information, 1973 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Financial information, 1972 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Financial information, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Wenner-Gren, 1970-1973 (Box 142, Folder 6)